Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as well,
so let's stay with the sun!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our radar is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the many roads.
That comes together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow is waiting
where we should be going, go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is calling out, so ride the wave.
We're all together as well,
so let's see when it's done.
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up.
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
Running forever. Let's go along
with curiosity. Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our minds will never give up There's a fire
in our dreams And you can never, never,
never, never stop it We
will be one, go ahead!
And so, the tiny ripples
all over the world
became a tidal wave before anyone noticed.
This isn't funny.
We got an arm still with it, though.
We hope that's happening.
What happens now?
I've been trying to call
the bastards all day.
but they won't pick up the damn snail.
What should we do?
What the hell can we do?
We're gonna die, that's what.
Get a load of this.
Those rookies we ran into back
on Sabo Odi formed an alliance.
Oh man, whatever it is, it can't be good!
Don't Flamingo resign,
but it doesn't say why?
There's gotta be a catch.
Hurry, contact everyone we know!
How did they find out about
our alliance so quick?
Who's the reporter? Opsa?
Never heard of him Some freelancer,
he's gotten a ton of scoops lately.
I'm not worried about our alliance.
It's the other news that troubles me,
Straw Hat and trafalgar bastards—so you're
looking to take on one of the emperors,
same as us?
Huh, I wonder which
one are you aiming for?
It's
me—I resigned.
Happy, he picked up finally.
Great, now what?
now what
Shh!
Just leave this to law!
Hello? This is Monkey D.
Luffy here, and I'm gonna be
king of the pirates! Damn it!
You do this every time! Hey! Mingo!
Are you Caesar's boss?
Because that guy really sucks, you know?
Sucks!
He did bad stuff to kids!
We'll give him back since
that's what we promised.
But if he does that again, we'll
kick his ass twice as hard!
And yours too!
I have a question for you.
After your brother Ace died,
Your crew disappeared for two years.
What were you doing all that time?
That's a secret!
Or I'm keeping it a
secret from you at least
I've actually been quite eager to see you.
I have something that will interest you.
Something you'll want very
badly, I'm quite certain.
Like meat?
Some kind of amazing super meat
like I've never tasted before
Cut it out.
He's toying with you, idiot.
What if it's a whole bunch of meat?
A whole meat?
Hey, it's up together.
Don't give him an edge,
even if it is meat.
Cut the crap.
We're handing over Caesar to you.
That was the deal.
No more, no less.
Well, that's for your
own good as much as mine.
We both know what will happen
if you try to run away with him.
That won't be a happy ending for anyone.
No meat, no meat.
Now, if you don't mind, I'd like to
speak to my business partner a moment.
I want to confirm he's nice and safe.
Oh, Joker, I'm so very sorry.
You resigned from the
Warlords all because of me.
He's fine, see?
Yeah, full of energy.
We'll meet eight hours from now
on an island north of Dressrosa.
We'll leave Caesar waiting for you
there at three in the afternoon.
Pick him up and this unpleasant
business will finally be over with.
Don't say that.
I wish we could sit down for a drink.
Such a shame.
Hang up already, Kudlik.
I'm sorry, guys.
They almost had me wrapped
up in his meat spell.
Yeah? Ya think?
Hey, wait.
We didn't specify how many
crewmates he can bring.
I don't get it.
Doflamingo's a big shot.
If he brings a whole army to the meeting
point, then we're screwed, right?
No, it's fine. Don't worry.
Handing over Caesar is just a distraction.
If it draws a ton of his resources,
that might even benefit us.
So you mean, if more people
come to the trade-off,
then less people will be
guarding the Smile Factory?
Yeah.
The question is, can we find the place?
You're kidding!
Hey, man, no problem.
We're not looking for
a needle in a haystack.
We're looking for a factory.
It's guaranteed to be big.
Once we get there, we'll find it
super easy. My lasers will take.
Care of the red, unfortunately I.
have intel on everything but the
factory no surprise really sounds
like it's their biggest asset
We might need to think outside
the box. We're going to Greenbit
but not the island of dress Rosa
itself that's most unfortunate
we're still docking the ship
address rosa just calm down have
you been to this dress nana place
before what was it like dress
rosa i've never been there
sorry do flamingo owns the place
Just like I always do,
I bet Mingo Kingdom's
gonna be crazy after
that we should swing by
Make things up?
If we're going in there
blind, we have to have a plan.
Sanji!
I'm hungry!
What's on the menu?
Sandwiches.
Did you say something about meat?
And milk for me.
Sorry, but I don't like bread.
Alas, I cannot divulge
why we were being pursued.
However, I will say that our original
destination was a place called Zoe.
Zoe? Huh?
You know it, Sir Law?
That's a rather convenient coincidence.
After I hand off Caesar, and destroyed
the Smile Factory like we planned.
Zoe was going to be the
next stop on my trip.
My crew's there.
They've been waiting.
If so, would it be possible to accompany
you there after our current mission?
Me too!
We'll all go to Wano! Very cool! Enough!
Momonosuke and three brave
samurai, including myself,
were headed to Zoe before
our ship was sadly destroyed.
I, Momonosuke, and another samurai
managed to make it to Dressrosa.
Once there, we...
We were assaulted by Doflamingo
and his villainous troop.
Panicked, I took refuge on a ship.
A dire mistake.
There, I met some children
being taken to Punk Hazard.
Soon, I shared in their terrible fate,
Though I had no idea what I
was in store for at the time.
Father! Momonosuke! No!
Surrounded and quite
desperate to follow the ship,
I relied on the brave
assistance of my fellow Samadai.
Kanjino.
Spare Mata-koth for me!
Protect Momonosuke!
If not for his sacrifice,
it all would have been lost!
I simply cannot leave him to die!
I must return to save him!
You're a real brother, Kanjuro.
Kanjuro!
OK, we'll help you save him.
No props. That's enough.
Stay focused.
Stick to our plan.
The seven warlords of the sea.
That's why we're here today.
As you know,
there are pirates who are excused of their
crimes by order of the
world government itself.
In return they provide us with two things:
overwhelming strength and intimidation.
In other words, although they
may be fearsome criminals,
the world government weaponizes their
prowess to keep other pirates in check.
First, the world's greatest
swordsman, Hawkeye Dracule Mihawk.
The King of Dressrosa and
the devilish puppeteer.
The heavenly demon,
Don Quixote Dothamingo.
Now, the Navy's human weapon,
the tyrant, Bartholomew Kumar.
The ruler of Amazon Lily,
Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock.
A member of the worst generation, and the
mastermind behind the Rocky Port incident.
The surgeon of death, Trafalgar Law.
At last, the founder and chief commander
of the Pirate Dispatch Organization.
A former crewmate of Roger,
whose fame continues to grow.
The genius jester, Bucky.
Those six, along with the
other guy, are warlords!
At least, they were?
That changed this morning
rather unexpectedly.
We don't know why, but Doflamingo quit.
Also, Law's under investigation.
It looks like we might have
to expel him from the group.
This is no good.
We need them to help balance the power
between the four emperors and us.
Don't worry, Brand New.
We're all on the same page here.
Fleet Admiral.
I'm not going to let Law and Straw
Hat make a mess of things on my watch.
Besides, I already had Smoker from G5
screaming my ear off in his last report.
That's when I said enough.
I said in, Fuji Dorry.
Your Majesty!
Please don't abandon us!
Hey, come on! Where are you?
Have you seen him, Sugar?
Nuh-uh.
Darn it.
The young master has a plan, I'm sure.
I just hope it involves a lot of fighting.
Come on, Navy, let's throw down!
Perhaps.
It's pointless to speculate now.
Oh, hey, Baby Five, looking for me?
What are you doing up there?
Wow, that crowd, they look mad.
Yeah, I bet the whole world's going crazy.
Hey, hey!
So, I heard the news.
You got a fiancé.
Or you got him killed, at least.
Haven't you ever heard of personal space?
Jeez, you're so annoying.
Annoying? But?
Annoying, but? What?
Hey, what?
But?
You like me! Is that it?
Would you drop this already?
The young master was calling you.
He wants you to bring...
the thing.
Now, please, go away!
Hey, hey, hey!
You gotta pick your fiancés better, or
Duffy's just gonna keep killing them!
But you know who Duffy
doesn't want to kill?
Me!
And you know who's single one
would make a good husband?
Also me!
Just yanking your chain.
You really need me.
I don't mind. Stop that!
The Colosseum is packed as usual.
Thanks for your hard work, Diamante.
The credit is all yours, Duffy.
This country owes everything
to its beloved king.
Beloved?
They're quite fond of you, too.
Stop.
You make it sound like I'm
the hero of the Colosseum.
Enough with the modesty.
That's exactly what you are.
No, no.
I'm nothing of the sort.
Fine, then.
You're not.
All right!
I'm a hero!
Guilty as charged! A hero!
Fearless and invincible!
But you didn't hear me say that.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I grabbed the thing you asked for.
Duffy, Duffy!
You're too close. Too close?
But what?
But I like it.
Now sit.
When Straw Hat finds out about this,
he'll do anything to get it;
then he'll be mine to control.
And his new friend law will
be dragged down with him,
diamante—I'm going to entrust this to you.
I couldn't possibly; it's
far too important—it's fine,
you'll know exactly what to do?
to do Stop.
You're making me sound
like some kind of genius.
Yes.
I can only entrust this to
a genius like you. No, no.
I'm nothing of the sort.
Fine, then. You're not.
All right, fine.
I'm a genius.
Guilty as charged.
A genius that will dispose
of that fool's Straw Hat.
But you didn't hear me say it, okay?
Don't worry, genius.
He won't be able to resist this one.
The source of his late brother's
power, the flame flame fruit.
He won't dare let anyone get
their hands on this thing.
Looming on the horizon
is their destination.
Those rocks!
Look, they're huge!
Dress Rosa, here we come!
Hey, won't you keep it down?
Dopo Bingo's gonna hear you!
Not likely.
Worry nuts, we're coming! Catch it all!
Known as a land of love and
passion, this is Dressrosa.
Hope you're ready for us, Bingo!
Dressrosa!
Let's party!
I told you to keep it down, Luffy!
Damn it!
What?
We're deep in enemy
territory, you know? Wow!
I just got the tests in, and guess what?
I'm extra super!
As soon as we find that factory,
then I'll let my lasers rip! Boo! Ah!
Okay, enough with the yelling, please!
I just had a great idea!
Momo!
Go!
Get off!
I am not going to town!
Also, I cannot fly!
I have to stay here!
What do you mean you can't fly?
I've seen you do it back
in that garbage shoe.
Remember, I don't—I have no
clue what you're talking about.
I'm not lying; he flew for real,
but he doesn't have wings, surely.
I would recall that, and even
if I could fly, I can't now.
If I did then then what's
your name?
It matters not.
The point is, I will never do
such a dreadful thing again.
I
won't fly; you can't make me.
What is your deal?
Afraid of heights or what?
what How dare you!
I am a brilliant samurai!
There is nothing in this
entire world that I fear!
Shut up and hop!
I'm on my fist!
Okay, he's only eight years old.
What the crap!
I don't care if I say it right!
I'm gonna be king of the
pirates all day! Ha! So what?
I shall be the shogun of Wano someday
And you'll be in the war beneath my face!
And if you're a worm or a eel,
then you're a monkey, you ape!
Yes, the wood monkeys are awesome!
Enough, Bobanosuke!
We owe him our lives!
Sir Luffy, please forgive him.
He is a samurai, but he is
still young and lacks restraint.
That said,
perhaps you could show some restraint in
dealing with children, for all our sakes.
If he's such a little coward,
maybe he shouldn't talk so big.
Curse it all!
Sorry!
Why is he picking on me?
Get off of her!
What's their problem?
Uh-huh.
Like father, like son.
You samurai are a bunch
of lechers, aren't you?
Mind your tongue, knave!
Hey, Kinemar, let's head to town.
How should we pervert, uh, I mean convert
our clothes so we don't stand out?
Oh, a disguise.
Yes, of course.
In Dressrosa, this fashion is
particularly important for women.
Allow me to produce appropriate costumes
so that we may enter the town safely.
I think I'm going to like
this Dressrosa place.
Give it a rest.
Hey.
Better take this.
It might come in handy.
It's a VIVRA card?
Yeah.
It'll take you to that place
called Zoe I mentioned.
Zoe is going to be the
next stop on my trip.
If anything happens to us on
Dressrosa, go straight there.
Just in case, right?
We should be fine. Who knows?
What's that paper?
A map one of my crew members made.
Kind of sloppy.
So this is where we're at,
the west coast of Dressrosa.
The Flamingo's palace is at the center.
We'll be responsible
for handing over Caesar.
We'll pass through Dressrosa until
we get to the northern shore.
There we'll cross a long bridge
to the island of Greenbit.
Why do we have to cross
Dressrosa to get to an island?
We could just take the ship, right?
Together!
I was told that's not possible.
Fine, sounds like fun.
Just get me there safely.
As for the Sunny security
team, be wary of enemy attacks.
You may have to be our decoy. Wait, what?
Is that a thing?
We might engage in combat? What?
I thought guarding duty
would be the safest.
Well, we are in enemy territory, right?
But that's okay, because
we've got Sanji to protect us.
He's not here! Sanji!
Luffy's team is gone, too!
They're the key to this whole plan.
They better not blow it.
Hey, forget about that for a second.
Who's going to protect us?
Those who travel here
may find their hearts
enchanted by any number of
the kingdom's many wonders.
For example, the fields of
beautiful, fragrant flowers.
Or perhaps the enticing
aroma of local cuisine.
Smells good!
After dinner, beautiful women and
passionate dancers may catch your eye.
Looks good!
And most remarkable of all...
Hey! Wait! Give it back!
Mario! Bad Dog! Bad Dog!
Give me back my arm!
It's not a toy! I need that!
What if the stuffing comes out, huh?
Then what am I gonna do?
Give me a break already!
All this money's giving me a side stitch!
And my stuffing!
Are they toys?
There is a strange sight that awestruck
visitors cannot see
anywhere else in the world.
Why, hello there.
Just a friendly neighborhood
soldier. Don't mind me.
Hmm, that's odd.
Have we met somewhere before?
I know your face.
Oh, that's it.
You are in today's paper.
Oh, no.
My strings got all tangled up.
Someone help me.
A toy or a dude?
Hey, Luffy, look at that.
Everywhere you look.
As if it were nothing peculiar at all.
There are toys.
Living alongside humans.
Only outsiders seem perplexed
by these colorful citizens.
Love, passion and toys.
Dance together in the streets
here in the port town.
Oh, man's been stabbed in the streets!
Oh, not again.
Did he say again?
You got some maniac on the loose?
Is that it?
No, just very passionate women.
And they're the jealous type, you know.
So if their lover cheats
on them, for example,
things get a little violent. A little?
Seems like the pretty ones
are especially stabby.
Okay, the toys are alive.
I'm over it now. Come on, let's eat.
Sir Luffy we cannot afford to whittle away
the hours in this place time is short.
I'm a citricongenal promptly
Whoa, whoa relax, bro.
I know we gotta move quick.
We can't go running around blind.
We gotta gather info first
Hey, isn't this fishy to you?
The king of the country abdicated
his throne this morning.
I kind of figured this place would be
in chaos, but nobody seems to care.
Maybe they haven't heard the news yet?
What no way!
Let's ask him, hey pups—stop it!
Why is that bad?
Because you were on the front
page of the newspaper today!
today
Thanks for waiting!
Your order has arrived!
Or has it?
Oh, yeah, I think it has! Let's eat!
Thresh shrimp Paulie...
Roast squid ink pasta...
And fairy pumpkin gazpacho!
Looks awesome!
It's time to dig in!
So good!
What the heck is a fairy pumpkin?
Well, uh, you see,
in this country, many people still
believe in old legends about fairies.
Or do they?
What kind of legend?
More like people see fairies. Or do they?
On the island?
Indeed.
All the time.
Fascinating, right?
It's been that way for centuries.
Although most of us have never
seen them, we all know they exist.
And do you know what people call them?
I'll tell you.
They call them the guardian
deities of Chris Rosa.
Or do they?
Ah, would you shut up?
He got it again.
That's 14 times in a row.
The party?
I wonder what their deal is.
It's a roulette table.
Let's go black for me.
What is it, friend?
Did I win or lose?
Black 20, you lose again.
White again, please.
Another black, wow!
This is a disgrace to the Don Quixote
name seems like all my luck ran out.
This is no good at all. Give
up, you had enough, old man.
We can really clean up
with Buffalo isn't here.
Keeping an eye on us, yeah.
No joking, not yet.
One last time, I'll bet
everything I've got.
That's the spirit.
You pick whatever color catches
your fancy, and I'll take the other.
Okay, of course, I'll bet
everything I've got as well.
You must be?
I'll be feeling lucky today.
Uh-huh.
All right, here goes.
Place your deck.
Everything on white, if you would, sir.
If you're set on choosing
white, I got only one option.
Everything on black.
Come on, white, win big!
It landed on White, didn't it?
Ha!
I've got some news to
bring to you, old timer.
It's White.
Who's the dealer here?
Maybe you should get
your eyes checked out.
Look more carefully this time.
Yep, it's White.
Congratulations, Gramps.
What?
Why don't you keep your mouth
shut and mind your own business?
Get lost.
Maybe he wants his ass kicked.
Who does this guy think he is?
Doesn't he know who they work for?
Got himself involved again.
You weren't pulling my
leg when you said I won?
Oh, you made off like a thief.
Sir, I don't know who you
are or where you came from,
but thank you for acting as my eyes.
I'm just calling it like I see it.
You made the bet.
Besides, you don't look like you
need help defending yourself.
You can't have stuck your
head where it doesn't belong.
If I say it landed on black,
then it landed on black.
He can't see anyway, so what difference
does it make what color I say it is?
We run this joint. You
got that. They left me no
choice i'm gonna have to
send every one of them
Why am i so happy
What?
Who the hell is this guy?
And how'd he do that?
Wow, that is one big hole.
It's not a curse to be blind
in this world of crime.
Everywhere you turn,
there's bound to be horrendous things
hardly worth laying your eyes upon.
Not seeing them is a true blessing.